popporn.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | POPPORN

##  Our Privacy Policy 

**Effective Date: 09/23/2015**

TLA realizes that making purchases online requires trust. We value our customer's trust and privacy and we pledge to you that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us. This includes, and is not limited to, any and all information you submit to us to complete an order, enter a contest or giveaway, or request information from TLA. 

TLA believes it is your right to know what information we may collect from you and how and why we may use it. This document helps to explain these procedures. 

TLA Entertainment Group, Inc. (TLA) is the owner and operator of tlavideo.com. We collect information from our customers that allow us to serve you, our customer, more effectively. 

TLA Entertainment Group, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [helpdesk@tlavideo.com](mailto:helpdesk@tlavideo.com) or 888-825-3837. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [www.tlavideo.com](http://www.tlavideo.com/). 

If you are a registered customer, you can change, modify or delete your personal information at any time by going to [My User Account](https://www.tlasecure.com/customer/userlogin.cfm?v=4&sn=1&g=0&go=%2Fcustomer%2Faccount%5Fmain%2Ecfm%3Fv%3D4%26g%3D0%26sn%3D1&domain=popporn.com&fsc=\(*CFID*!2.40306325E8,*sn*!1,*CFTOKEN*!1.5091156E7,*ic*!false\)&adult_pass=y). Log in with your email address and password, click "Account Information" and edit your personal information as you wish. 

##  1\. Personal information we collect 

We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using the TLA website. This information includes your name, email address and a password when you register to create your tlavideo.com account. You are able to browse our site and place an order without registering, but you will need to do so in order to take advantage of special TLA features. We may also ask you for personal information when you contact our customer service department. This is necessary so we can protect against fraud and to process your request more efficiently. 

###  Purchase information 

When you place an order with tlavideo.com, we collect your name, email address, phone number, billing and shipping addresses, credit card number, expiration date and identification code if applicable. This information is important in processing your order and verifying your billing address. It also allows us to ship your order and keep you informed regarding the status of your order. Billing information can be provided over the phone by calling our customer service department at 1.800.333.8521x1. 

If you are a registered customer of tlavideo.com, you can save your shipping address or billing information for one or more credit cards in [My User Account](https://www.tlasecure.com/customer/userlogin.cfm?v=4&sn=1&g=0&go=%2Fcustomer%2Faccount%5Fmain%2Ecfm%3Fv%3D4%26g%3D0%26sn%3D1&domain=popporn.com&fsc=\(*CFID*!2.40306325E8,*sn*!1,*CFTOKEN*!1.5091156E7,*ic*!false\)&adult_pass=y). You may change or delete this information at any time by clicking on [My User Account](https://www.tlasecure.com/customer/userlogin.cfm?v=4&sn=1&g=0&go=%2Fcustomer%2Faccount%5Fmain%2Ecfm%3Fv%3D4%26g%3D0%26sn%3D1&domain=popporn.com&fsc=\(*CFID*!2.40306325E8,*sn*!1,*CFTOKEN*!1.5091156E7,*ic*!false\)&adult_pass=y). Log in using your email address and password, then you may change or delete any personal information that you like. 

###  Cookies and other computer information 

When you visit the TLA website, you will be assigned a "cookie" (a small unique identifier text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of this cookie is to identify you when you visit our site so we can enhance and customize your shopping experience. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. 

Your browser must be set to accept this "cookie" for you to be able to shop on tlavideo.com. You can delete this "cookie" on your computer once you have completed shopping. To delete a cookie on your browser refer to the "Help" menu on your particular browser. 

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by TLA and our marketing and site customization partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers and chat providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 or Flash to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. For information on how to manage Flash LSOs please click [here.](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

###  Other times we may collect personal information 

From time to time, TLA may conduct contests and/or giveaways using our Website, email, or other media. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. If you choose to participate, we may require you to supply personal information such as email and/or postal mailing information. We treat this information with the same policies as outlined in this document. 

We will use your email address that you provide to respond to your questions, suggestions, to send participants an email newsletter, and/or requests for assistance in using tlavideo.com. 

We do not currently use a third party service provider to conduct these contests or giveaways (though we reserve the right to do so in future); if we do ever use a third party service, that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personal information for any other purpose. We will not share the personal information you provide through a contest or giveaway with other third parties. 

##  2\. Use of your personal information 

Information we collect may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways: 

  * Information we collect on tlavideo.com may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:
  * Deliver products that you purchase online
  * Register you as a customer of TLA
  * Bill your credit card for purchases you make on tlavideo.com
  * Confirm your shopping orders
  * Respond to your customer service inquiries and/or requests
  * Communicate special sales, offers, features, contests, giveaways, etc. that may be of interest to you if you choose to receive such notices
  * Find and stock the products you want
  * Customize your experience at tlavideo.com

##  3\. When and with whom we share your personal information 

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. 

We never sell or rent your billing or credit card information to any third parties under any circumstance. We will share customer information only with our agents, representatives and trusted service providers and contractors for the limited purposes of fulfilling customer orders such as a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services and a shipping company to fulfill orders; offering certain products and services in connection with our Website; communication to customers; providing customer service via live chat software; enhancing and improving the customer shopping experience; providing a personalized shopping experience and completing credit card transactions. 

We will not share your email address with any third party without your explicit consent. Occasionally we run promotions on our site, which may include the opportunity to opt-in to email lists for specific partner companies. In these cases, sharing your email address will not be required and the promotion will include specific information about how your email address will be shared. 

On occasion, we partner with other major companies whose products or services we feel offer the same high quality and standards as our own. In these instances our postal mailing lists are made available to them. While we carefully pick and choose whom we partner with, we understand perfectly if you prefer to hear from no one but us. To remain exclusively with us and not receive information about any other companies or their services, please call us at 1-800-333-8521, ext. 1 or e-mail [helpdesk@tlavideo.com](mailto:helpdesk@tlavideo.com). You can also go to the [My User Account](https://www.tlasecure.com/customer/userlogin.cfm?v=4&sn=1&g=0&go=%2Fcustomer%2Faccount%5Fmain%2Ecfm%3Fv%3D4%26g%3D0%26sn%3D1&domain=popporn.com&fsc=\(*CFID*!2.40306325E8,*sn*!1,*CFTOKEN*!1.5091156E7,*ic*!false\)&adult_pass=y) section of our site and under the Mailing List Preferences tab select the option (at the bottom of the page) for "I do not wish to have my information shared with third parties." 

Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, or similar legal process. 

In the event TLA goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

##  4\. How you can decide what marketing communication your receive from us 

If you choose to receive them, tlavideo.com will periodically send you email messages describing new products, featured merchandise and special promotions and/or giveaways. You can choose to stop receiving these emails at any time. Simply go to Email Preferences, enter your email address to view your preferences, and unclick any box currently checked in our email subscriber list. You may also choose to no longer receive these email communications by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each of the emails you receive. 

If you select not to receive any marketing emails as described above, we may occasionally send a general email to our existing non-subscribed customers encouraging them to opt-in. You may opt out of receiving them as above. We may also need to send operational emails to inform you of any changes to our site that might affect your personal information. If you would prefer to receive no email from TLA ever, simply go to Email Preferences, enter your email address to view your preferences, and click the box "I do not wish to receive any e-mail". We may also need to contact you about a problem with an order you placed. If you don't want to be contacted via e-mail and would prefer phone contact, please call our customer service department at 800-333-8521 x1. 

If you choose to receive product alerts within your user account we will occasionally send you emails based upon your request. If you would like to change the frequency with which you receive alerts or if you no longer wish to receive them simply go to [My User Account](https://www.tlasecure.com/customer/userlogin.cfm?v=4&sn=1&g=0&go=%2Fcustomer%2Faccount%5Fmain%2Ecfm%3Fv%3D4%26g%3D0%26sn%3D1&domain=popporn.com&fsc=\(*CFID*!2.40306325E8,*sn*!1,*CFTOKEN*!1.5091156E7,*ic*!false\)&adult_pass=y), long in, click on “Alerts” and make the appropriate selections. 

The only email you will receive from tlavideo.com if you are not subscribed to our email list will be to confirm any purchases you make on our site, let you know your order has been shipped, respond to any customer service inquiries and to answer any other questions you might have about our site. 

##  5\. Accessing your personal information 

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, delete or update it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [helpdesk@tlavideo.com](mailto:helpdesk@tlavideo.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [helpdesk@tlavideo.com](mailto:helpdesk@tlavideo.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

##  6\. How we protect the security of your personal information 

The security of your personal information is as important to TLA as it is to you. TLA uses a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). TLA has obtained a digital certificate from [GeoTrust, Inc.](https://www.geotrust.com/) When you enter a secure section of the TLA site, an image of a closed lock or a solid key should appear in the bottom bar of your browser. If you click on this image, a small pop-up window displaying site-security information will appear. The digital certificate guarantees that your personal information and/or sensitive information (such as a credit card number) is being transmitted to the secure and encrypted TLA Web server. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [helpdesk@tlavideo.com.](mailto:helpdesk@tlavideo.com)

Your personal information is protected by the password you created when you registered an account at TLA. It is your responsibility to keep this password confidential. You may change this password at any time by going to [My User Account](https://www.tlasecure.com/customer/userlogin.cfm?v=4&sn=1&g=0&go=%2Fcustomer%2Faccount%5Fmain%2Ecfm%3Fv%3D4%26g%3D0%26sn%3D1&domain=popporn.com&fsc=\(*CFID*!2.40306325E8,*sn*!1,*CFTOKEN*!1.5091156E7,*ic*!false\)&adult_pass=y). Log in with your email address and password and then click "Account Information" and enter a new password. 

##  7\. Links to other sites 

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of TLA. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

##  8\. Customer reviews 

We post customer reviews on our web site which may contain personal information. These reviews are moderated prior to posting, and if you wish to request the removal of your review you may do so by contacting us at [helpdesk@tlavideo.com](mailto:helpdesk@tlavideo.com). 

##  9\. Social Media Widgets 

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

##  10\. Wishlists 

When you add a product to your wish list, those items will NOT be listed in our publicly accessible wishlist directory. You may make all or a portion of your wish list products public at your discretion; go to [My User Account](https://www.tlasecure.com/customer/userlogin.cfm?v=4&sn=1&g=0&go=%2Fcustomer%2Faccount%5Fmain%2Ecfm%3Fv%3D4%26g%3D0%26sn%3D1&domain=popporn.com&fsc=\(*CFID*!2.40306325E8,*sn*!1,*CFTOKEN*!1.5091156E7,*ic*!false\)&adult_pass=y), select “Wishlist” and make the appropriate selections. 

##  11\. Changes to the TLA Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this privacy policy at any time. If we make any material change to this policy, we will post a prominent notice of the change on tlavideo.com prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

##  12\. How to contact TLA 

If you have a problem regarding an order, or want more information on a particular title, please see our Customer Service page, or call us at 888-TLA-DVDS, ext.1 (Mon-Fri, 10:00am-10:00pm ET; Sat, Noon-8pm ET). 

If you are experiencing technical problems with our site, please see our Customer Service page. 

To reach our corporate office: 

  * TLA Entertainment Group, Inc.
  * 110 S. 7th Street - 3rd Floor
  * Philadelphia PA 19106
  * United States of America
  * Phone: 1-215-733-0608 (ext. 1)
  * Fax: 1-267-765-9882
  * Email: [helpdesk@tlavideo.com](mailto:helpdesk@tlavideo.com) or simply use the form below.
